vipsociety.com 2012-09-24

# privacy policy

the following text is intellectual property of datasteam technologies and copying is strictly prohibited 

This privacy policy sets out how uses and protects any information that you provide when you use this website.

We are committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

We may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes.

### What we collect

We may collect the following information:

  * your name, profile picture and date of birth 

  * the email address you used to create a stand alone account or shared through facebook 

  * your facebook numeric id when facebook is used to connect 

  * your public IP address which is publicly provided by your Internet Service Provider

  * all data generated in the application

### What we do with the information we gather

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

  * Internal record keeping.

  * Notify you about ingame activity

  * We may use the information to improve our products and services.

  * We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.

  * We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests.

### Security

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

### How we use cookies

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to your website. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [advertising opt-out page](http://www.google.com/privacy/ads/). 

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about webpage traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

### Links to other websites

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

### Private messages in vipsociety.com

Private chat is just private. That means no other player, guard, agent, editor or unathorized user can see what you two say to each other. But you should avoid sending sensitive personal information such as passwords or credit card numbers. Please also note that your private posts are subject to your home country's applicable laws and we take no responsibility for them. You can also use the application provided report feature to report inappropriate content in order to take appropriate action.

### Controlling your personal information

You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:

  * whenever you feel that you want to remove yourself from the game you can deactivate your account using the ingame account control panel or the default facebook application removal procedure in case you are using your facebook account to access vipsociety.com

  * send us an email at support@vipsociety.com

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please email us as soon as possible, at the support@grablocked.com and we will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
